Navigation Menu
---------------

Toggle navigation

* Product
    
    * [GitHub Copilot
        
        Write better code with AI](https://github.com/features/copilot)
    * [Security
        
        Find and fix vulnerabilities](https://github.com/features/security)
    * [Actions
        
        Automate any workflow](https://github.com/features/actions)
    * [Codespaces
        
        Instant dev environments](https://github.com/features/codespaces)
    * [Issues
        
        Plan and track work](https://github.com/features/issues)
    * [Code Review
        
        Manage code changes](https://github.com/features/code-review)
    * [Discussions
        
        Collaborate outside of code](https://github.com/features/discussions)
    * [Code Search
        
        Find more, search less](https://github.com/features/code-search)
    
    Explore

* Solutions
    
    By company size

    By use case

    By industry

* Resources
    
    Topics

    Explore

* Open Source
    
    * [GitHub Sponsors
        
        Fund open source developers](https://github.com/sponsors)
    
    * [The ReadME Project
        
        GitHub community articles](https://github.com/readme)
    
    Repositories

* Enterprise
    
    * [Enterprise platform
        
        AI-powered developer platform](https://github.com/enterprise)
    
    Available add-ons
    
    * [Advanced Security
        
        Enterprise-grade security features](https://github.com/enterprise/advanced-security)
    * [GitHub Copilot
        
        Enterprise-grade AI features](https://github.com/features/copilot#enterprise)
    * [Premium Support
        
        Enterprise-grade 24/7 support](https://github.com/premium-support)

Search or jump to...

Search code, repositories, users, issues, pull requests...
==========================================================

Search

Clear

Provide feedback
================

We read every piece of feedback, and take your input very seriously.

 Include my email address so I can be contacted

Cancel Submit feedback

Saved searches
==============

Use saved searches to filter your results more quickly
------------------------------------------------------

Name  

Query 

To see all available qualifiers, see our [documentation](https://docs.github.com/search-github/github-code-search/understanding-github-code-search-syntax).

Cancel Create saved search

[Sign up](https://github.com/signup?ref_cta=Sign+up&ref_loc=header+logged+out&ref_page=%2F%3Cuser-name%3E%2F%3Crepo-name%3E%2Fblob%2Fshow&source=header-repo&source_repo=gorilla-devs%2FGDLauncher) Reseting focus

You signed in with another tab or window. Reload to refresh your session. You signed out in another tab or window. Reload to refresh your session. You switched accounts on another tab or window. Reload to refresh your session. Dismiss alert

[gorilla-devs](https://github.com/gorilla-devs) / **[GDLauncher](https://github.com/gorilla-devs/GDLauncher)** Public

* [Notifications](https://github.com/login?return_to=%2Fgorilla-devs%2FGDLauncher) You must be signed in to change notification settings

Additional navigation options

  Files
-----

 master

Breadcrumbs
-----------

1. [GDLauncher](https://github.com/gorilla-devs/GDLauncher/tree/master)
2. /[src](https://github.com/gorilla-devs/GDLauncher/tree/master/src)
3. /[common](https://github.com/gorilla-devs/GDLauncher/tree/master/src/common)
4. /[components](https://github.com/gorilla-devs/GDLauncher/tree/master/src/common/components)

/

PrivacyPolicy.js
================

Blame

Blame

Latest commit
-------------

History
-------

738 lines (736 loc) · 37.1 KB

 master

Breadcrumbs
-----------

1. [GDLauncher](https://github.com/gorilla-devs/GDLauncher/tree/master)
2. /[src](https://github.com/gorilla-devs/GDLauncher/tree/master/src)
3. /[common](https://github.com/gorilla-devs/GDLauncher/tree/master/src/common)
4. /[components](https://github.com/gorilla-devs/GDLauncher/tree/master/src/common/components)

/

PrivacyPolicy.js
================

Top

File metadata and controls
--------------------------

* Code
    
* Blame

738 lines (736 loc) · 37.1 KB

1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10

11

12

13

14

15

16

17

18

19

20

21

22

23

24

25

26

27

28

29

30

31

32

33

34

35

36

37

38

39

40

41

42

43

44

45

46

47

48

49

50

51

52

53

54

55

56

57

58

59

60

61

62

63

64

65

66

67

68

69

70

71

72

73

74

75

76

77

78

79

80

81

82

83

84

85

86

87

88

89

90

91

92

93

94

95

96

97

98

99

100

101

102

103

104

105

106

107

108

109

110

111

112

113

114

115

116

117

118

119

120

121

122

123

124

125

126

127

128

129

130

131

132

133

134

135

136

137

138

139

140

141

142

143

144

145

146

147

148

149

150

151

152

153

154

155

156

157

158

159

160

161

162

163

164

165

166

167

168

169

170

171

172

173

174

175

176

177

178

179

180

181

182

183

184

185

186

187

188

189

190

191

192

193

194

195

196

197

198

199

200

201

202

203

204

205

206

207

208

209

210

211

212

213

214

215

216

217

218

219

220

221

222

223

224

225

226

227

228

229

230

231

232

233

234

235

236

237

238

239

240

241

242

243

244

245

246

247

248

249

250

251

252

253

254

255

256

257

258

259

260

261

262

263

264

265

266

267

268

269

270

271

272

273

274

275

276

277

278

279

280

281

282

283

284

285

286

287

288

289

290

291

292

293

294

295

296

297

298

299

300

301

302

303

304

305

306

307

308

309

310

311

312

313

314

315

316

317

318

319

320

321

322

323

324

325

326

327

328

329

330

331

332

333

334

335

336

337

338

339

340

341

342

343

344

345

346

347

348

349

350

351

352

353

354

355

356

357

358

359

360

361

362

363

364

365

366

367

368

369

370

371

372

373

374

375

376

377

378

379

380

381

382

383

384

385

386

387

388

389

390

391

392

393

394

395

396

397

398

399

400

401

402

403

404

405

406

407

408

409

410

411

412

413

414

415

416

417

418

419

420

421

422

423

424

425

426

427

428

429

430

431

432

433

434

435

436

437

438

439

440

441

442

443

444

445

446

447

448

449

450

451

452

453

454

455

456

457

458

459

460

461

462

463

464

465

466

467

468

469

470

471

472

473

474

475

476

477

478

479

480

481

482

483

484

485

486

487

488

489

490

491

492

493

494

495

496

497

498

499

500

501

502

503

504

505

506

507

508

509

510

511

512

513

514

515

516

517

518

519

520

521

522

523

524

525

526

527

528

529

530

531

532

533

534

535

536

537

538

539

540

541

542

543

544

545

546

547

548

549

550

551

552

553

554

555

556

557

558

559

560

561

562

563

564

565

566

567

568

569

570

571

572

573

574

575

576

577

578

579

580

581

582

583

584

585

586

587

588

589

590

591

592

593

594

595

596

597

598

599

600

601

602

603

604

605

606

607

608

609

610

611

612

613

614

615

616

617

618

619

620

621

622

623

624

625

626

627

628

629

630

631

632

633

634

635

636

637

638

639

640

641

642

643

644

645

646

647

648

649

650

651

652

653

654

655

656

657

658

659

660

661

662

663

664

665

666

667

668

669

670

671

672

673

674

675

676

677

678

679

680

681

682

683

684

685

686

687

688

689

690

691

692

693

694

695

696

697

698

699

700

701

702

703

704

705

706

707

708

709

710

711

712

713

714

715

716

717

718

719

720

721

722

723

724

725

726

727

728

729

730

731

732

733

734

735

736

737

738

import React, { memo } from 'react';

const PrivacyPolicy \= () \=> {

return (

<\>

<h1\>Privacy Policy</h1\>

<div\>

<h2\>Introduction</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through

our compliance with this privacy policy (“Policy”). This Policy

describes the types of information we may collect from you or that

you may provide (“Personal Information”) on the{' '}

<a

target\="\_blank"

rel\="nofollow noreferrer"

href\="https://gdlauncher.com"

\>

gdlauncher.com

</a\>{' '}

website (“Website”), “GDLauncher” application (“Application”), and

any of their related products and services (collectively,

“Services”), and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining,

protecting, and disclosing that Personal Information. It also

describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your

Personal Information and how you can access and update it.

</p\>

<p\>

This Policy is a legally binding agreement between you (“User”,

“you” or “your”) and this Website operator and Application developer

(“Operator”, “we”, “us” or “our”). If you are entering into this

agreement on behalf of a business or other legal entity, you

represent that you have the authority to bind such entity to this

agreement, in which case the terms “User”, “you” or “your” shall

refer to such entity. If you do not have such authority, or if you

do not agree with the terms of this agreement, you must not accept

this agreement and may not access and use the Services. By accessing

and using the Services, you acknowledge that you have read,

understood, and agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy. This

Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not

own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Automatic collection of information</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

When you open the Website or use the Application, our servers

automatically record information that your browser or device sends.

This data may include information such as your device’s IP address

and location, browser and device name and version, operating system

type and version, language preferences, the webpage you were

visiting before you came to the Services, pages of the Services that

you visit, the time spent on those pages, the information you search

for on the Services, access times and dates, and other statistics.

</p\>

<p\>

Information collected automatically is used only to identify

potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information

regarding the usage and traffic of the Services. This statistical

information is not otherwise aggregated in such a way that would

identify any particular User of the system.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Collection of personal information</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

You can access and use the Services without telling us who you are

or revealing any information by which someone could identify you as

a specific, identifiable individual. If, however, you wish to use

some of the features offered on the Services, you may be asked to

provide certain Personal Information (for example, your name and

e-mail address).

</p\>

<p\>

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us

when you create an account, publish content, make a purchase, or

fill any online forms on the Services. When required, this

information may include the following:

</p\>

<ul\>

<li\>

Account details (such as user name, unique user ID, password, etc)

</li\>

<li\>

Contact information (such as email address, phone number, etc)

</li\>

<li\>

Any other materials you willingly submit to us (such as articles,

images, feedback, etc)

</li\>

</ul\>

<p\>

Some of the information we collect is directly from you via the

Services. However, we may also collect Personal Information about

you from other sources such as public databases, social media

platforms, third-party data providers, and our joint marketing

partners. Personal Information we collect from other sources may

include demographic information, such as age and gender, device

information, such as IP addresses, location, such as city and state,

and online behavioral data, such as information about your use of

social media websites, page view information and search results and

links.

</p\>

<p\>

You can choose not to provide us with your Personal Information, but

then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the features

on the Services. Users who are uncertain about what information is

mandatory are welcome to contact us.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Privacy of children</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children

under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not

submit any Personal Information through the Services. If you have

reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided

Personal Information to us through the Services, please contact us

to request that we delete that child’s Personal Information from our

Services.

</p\>

<p\>

We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s

Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their

children never to provide Personal Information through the Services

without their permission. We also ask that all parents and legal

guardians overseeing the care of children take the necessary

precautions to ensure that their children are instructed to never

give out Personal Information when online without their permission.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Use and processing of collected information</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

We act as a data controller and a data processor in terms of the

GDPR when handling Personal Information, unless we have entered into

a data processing agreement with you in which case you would be the

data controller and we would be the data processor.

</p\>

<p\>

Our role may also differ depending on the specific situation

involving Personal Information. We act in the capacity of a data

controller when we ask you to submit your Personal Information that

is necessary to ensure your access and use of the Services. In such

instances, we are a data controller because we determine the

purposes and means of the processing of Personal Information and we

comply with data controllers’ obligations set forth in the GDPR.

</p\>

<p\>

We act in the capacity of a data processor in situations when you

submit Personal Information through the Services. We do not own,

control, or make decisions about the submitted Personal Information,

and such Personal Information is processed only in accordance with

your instructions. In such instances, the User providing Personal

Information acts as a data controller in terms of the GDPR.

</p\>

<p\>

In order to make the Services available to you, or to meet a legal

obligation, we may need to collect and use certain Personal

Information. If you do not provide the information that we request,

we may not be able to provide you with the requested products or

services. Any of the information we collect from you may be used for

the following purposes:

</p\>

<ul\>

<li\>Create and manage user accounts</li\>

<li\>Deliver products or services</li\>

<li\>Improve products and services</li\>

<li\>Send product and service updates</li\>

<li\>Respond to inquiries and offer support</li\>

<li\>Request user feedback</li\>

<li\>Improve user experience</li\>

<li\>Protect from abuse and malicious users</li\>

<li\>Run and operate the Services</li\>

</ul\>

<p\>

Processing your Personal Information depends on how you interact

with the Services, where you are located in the world and if one of

the following applies: (i) you have given your consent for one or

more specific purposes; this, however, does not apply, whenever the

processing of Personal Information is subject to California Consumer

Privacy Act or European data protection law; (ii) provision of

information is necessary for the performance of an agreement with

you and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof; (iii)

processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to

which you are subject; (iv) processing is related to a task that is

carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official

authority vested in us; (v) processing is necessary for the purposes

of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party.

</p\>

<p\>

We rely on the following legal bases as defined in the GDPR upon

which we collect and process your Personal Information:

</p\>

<ul\>

<li\>User’s consent</li\>

<li\>Performance of a contract</li\>

<li\>Our own legitimate interests</li\>

</ul\>

<p\>

Note that under some legislations we may be allowed to process

information until you object to such processing by opting out,

without having to rely on consent or any other of the legal bases

above. In any case, we will be happy to clarify the specific legal

basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the

provision of Personal Information is a statutory or contractual

requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Payment processing</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

In case of Services requiring payment, you may need to provide your

credit card details or other payment account information, which will

be used solely for processing payments. We use third-party payment

processors (“Payment Processors”) to assist us in processing your

payment information securely.

</p\>

<p\>

Payment Processors adhere to the latest security standards as

managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint

effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and

Discover. Sensitive and private data exchange happens over a SSL

secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with

digital signatures, and the Services are also in compliance with

strict vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an

environment as possible for Users. We will share payment data with

the Payment Processors only to the extent necessary for the purposes

of processing your payments, refunding such payments, and dealing

with complaints and queries related to such payments and refunds.

</p\>

<p\>

Please note that the Payment Processors may collect some Personal

Information from you, which allows them to process your payments

(e.g., your email address, address, credit card details, and bank

account number) and handle all the steps in the payment process

through their systems, including data collection and data

processing. The Payment Processors’ use of your Personal Information

is governed by their respective privacy policies which may or may

not contain privacy protections as protective as this Policy. We

suggest that you review their respective privacy policies.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Managing information</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

You are able to delete certain Personal Information we have about

you. The Personal Information you can delete may change as the

Services change. When you delete Personal Information, however, we

may maintain a copy of the unrevised Personal Information in our

records for the duration necessary to comply with our obligations to

our affiliates and partners, and for the purposes described below.

If you would like to delete your Personal Information or permanently

delete your account, you can do so by contacting us.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Disclosure of information</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

Depending on the requested Services or as necessary to complete any

transaction or provide any Service you have requested, we may share

your information with our affiliates, contracted companies, and

service providers (collectively, “Service Providers”) we rely upon

to assist in the operation of the Services available to you and

whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to

abide by our policies with respect to Personal Information. We will

not share any personally identifiable information with third parties

and will not share any information with unaffiliated third parties.

</p\>

<p\>

Service Providers are not authorized to use or disclose your

information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or

comply with legal requirements. Service Providers are given the

information they need only in order to perform their designated

functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose any of

the provided information for their own marketing or other purposes.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Retention of information</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

We will retain and use your Personal Information for the period

necessary to comply with our legal obligations, as long as your user

account remains active, to enforce our agreements, resolve disputes,

and unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by

law.

</p\>

<p\>

We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your

Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a

manner that would identify you personally. Once the retention period

expires, Personal Information shall be deleted. Therefore, the right

to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification, and the

right to data portability cannot be enforced after the expiration of

the retention period.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Transfer of information</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

Depending on your location, data transfers may involve transferring

and storing your information in a country other than your own. The

transfer of your Personal Information to countries outside the

European Union will be made only if you have explicitly consented to

it or in the cases provided for by the GDPR and will be processed in

your interest.

</p\>

<p\>

You are entitled to learn about the legal basis of information

transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any

international organization governed by public international law or

set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the

security measures taken by us to safeguard your information. If any

such transfer takes place, you can find out more by checking the

relevant sections of this Policy or inquire with us using the

information provided in the contact section.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Data protection rights under the GDPR</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), you

have certain data protection rights and we aim to take reasonable

steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of

your Personal Information. If you wish to be informed what Personal

Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from

our systems, please contact us. In certain circumstances, you have

the following data protection rights:

</p\>

<p\>

(i) You have the right to withdraw consent where you have previously

given your consent to the processing of your Personal Information.

To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your

Personal Information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that

consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of

processing before the withdrawal.

</p\>

<p\>

(ii) You have the right to learn if your Personal Information is

being processed by us, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects

of the processing, and obtain a copy of your Personal Information

undergoing processing.

</p\>

<p\>

(iii) You have the right to verify the accuracy of your information

and ask for it to be updated or corrected. You also have the right

to request us to complete the Personal Information you believe is

incomplete.

</p\>

<p\>

(iv) You have the right to object to the processing of your

information if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other

than consent. Where Personal Information is processed for the public

interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in us, or

for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us, you may

object to such processing by providing a ground related to your

particular situation to justify the objection. You must know that,

however, should your Personal Information be processed for direct

marketing purposes, you can object to that processing at any time

without providing any justification. To learn whether we are

processing Personal Information for direct marketing purposes, you

may refer to the relevant sections of this Policy.

</p\>

<p\>

(v) You have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the

processing of your Personal Information. These circumstances

include: the accuracy of your Personal Information is contested by

you and we must verify its accuracy; the processing is unlawful, but

you oppose the erasure of your Personal Information and request the

restriction of its use instead; we no longer need your Personal

Information for the purposes of processing, but you require it to

establish, exercise or defend your legal claims; you have objected

to processing pending the verification of whether our legitimate

grounds override your legitimate grounds. Where processing has been

restricted, such Personal Information will be marked accordingly

and, with the exception of storage, will be processed only with your

consent or for the establishment, to exercise or defense of legal

claims, for the protection of the rights of another natural, or

legal person or for reasons of important public interest.

</p\>

<p\>

(vi) You have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the

erasure of your Personal Information from us. These circumstances

include: the Personal Information is no longer necessary in relation

to the purposes for which it was collected or otherwise processed;

you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; you object to the

processing under certain rules of applicable data protection law;

the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the personal

data have been unlawfully processed. However, there are exclusions

of the right to erasure such as where processing is necessary: for

exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for

compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, to

exercise or defense of legal claims.

</p\>

<p\>

(vii) You have the right to receive your Personal Information that

you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used, and

machine-readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it

transmitted to another controller without any hindrance from us,

provided that such transmission does not adversely affect the rights

and freedoms of others.

</p\>

<p\>

(viii) You have the right to complain to a data protection authority

about our collection and use of your Personal Information. If you

are not satisfied with the outcome of your complaint directly with

us, you have the right to lodge a complaint with your local data

protection authority. For more information, please contact your

local data protection authority in the EEA. This provision is

applicable provided that your Personal Information is processed by

automated means and that the processing is based on your consent, on

a contract which you are part of, or on pre-contractual obligations

thereof.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>California privacy rights</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

Consumers residing in California are afforded certain additional

rights with respect to their Personal Information under the

California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”). If you are a California

resident, this section applies to you.

</p\>

<p\>

In addition to the rights as explained in this Policy, California

residents who provide Personal Information as defined in the statute

to obtain Services for personal, family, or household use are

entitled to request and obtain from us, once a calendar year,

information about the categories and specific pieces of Personal

Information we have collected and disclosed.

</p\>

<p\>

Furthermore, California residents have the right to request deletion

of their Personal Information or opt-out of the sale of their

Personal Information which may include selling, disclosing, or

transferring Personal Information to another business or a third

party for monetary or other valuable consideration. To do so, simply

contact us. We will not discriminate against you if you exercise

your rights under the CCPA.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>How to exercise your rights</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

Any requests to exercise your rights can be directed to us through

the contact details provided in this document. Please note that we

may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such

requests. Your request must provide sufficient information that

allows us to verify that you are the person you are claiming to be

or that you are the authorized representative of such person. If we

receive your request from an authorized representative, we may

request evidence that you have provided such an authorized

representative with power of attorney or that the authorized

representative otherwise has valid written authority to submit

requests on your behalf.

</p\>

<p\>

You must include sufficient details to allow us to properly

understand the request and respond to it. We cannot respond to your

request or provide you with Personal Information unless we first

verify your identity or authority to make such a request and confirm

that the Personal Information relates to you.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Cookies</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

Our Services use “cookies” to help personalize your online

experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk

by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or

deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to

you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued

the cookie to you. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be

able to fully experience the features of the Services. You may learn

more about cookies and how they work{' '}

<a

target\="\_blank"

href\="https://www.websitepolicies.com/blog/cookies"

rel\="noreferrer"

\>

here

</a\>

.

</p\>

<p\>

We may use cookies to collect, store, and track information for

security and personalization, to operate the Services, and for

statistical purposes. Please note that you have the ability to

accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept

cookies by default, but you can modify your browser settings to

decline cookies if you prefer.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Data analytics</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

Our Services may use third-party analytics tools that use cookies,

web beacons, or other similar information-gathering technologies to

collect standard internet activity and usage information. The

information gathered is used to compile statistical reports on User

activity such as how often Users visit our Services, what pages they

visit and for how long, etc. We use the information obtained from

these analytics tools to monitor the performance and improve our

Services.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Do Not Track signals</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

Some browsers incorporate a Do Not Track feature that signals to

websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity

tracked. Tracking is not the same as using or collecting information

in connection with a website. For these purposes, tracking refers to

collecting personally identifiable information from consumers who

use or visit a website or online service as they move across

different websites over time. How browsers communicate the Do Not

Track signal is not yet uniform. As a result, the Services are not

yet set up to interpret or respond to Do Not Track signals

communicated by your browser. Even so, as described in more detail

throughout this Policy, we limit our use and collection of your

Personal Information.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Advertisements</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

We may display online advertisements and we may share aggregated and

non-identifying information about our customers that we or our

advertisers collect through your use of the Services. We do not

share personally identifiable information about individual customers

with advertisers. In some instances, we may use this aggregated and

non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements to

the intended audience.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Social media features</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

Our Services may include social media features, such as the Facebook

and Twitter buttons, Share This buttons, etc (collectively, “Social

Media Features”). These Social Media Features may collect your IP

address, what page you are visiting on our Services, and may set a

cookie to enable Social Media Features to function properly. Social

Media Features are hosted either by their respective providers or

directly on our Services. Your interactions with these Social Media

Features are governed by the privacy policy of their respective

providers.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Email marketing</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

We offer electronic newsletters to which you may voluntarily

subscribe at any time. We are committed to keeping your e-mail

address confidential and will not disclose your email address to any

third parties except as allowed in the information use and

processing section or for the purposes of utilizing a third-party

provider to send such emails. We will maintain the information sent

via e-mail in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

</p\>

<p\>

In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mails sent from us will

clearly state who the e-mail is from and provide clear information

on how to contact the sender. You may choose to stop receiving our

newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe

instructions included in these emails or by contacting us. However,

you will continue to receive essential transactional emails.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Affiliate links</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

We may engage in affiliate marketing and have affiliate links

present on the Services for the purpose of being able to offer you

related or additional products and services. If you click on an

affiliate link, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any

sales for purposes of commissions.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Links to other resources</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

The Services contain links to other resources that are not owned or

controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for

the privacy practices of such other resources or third parties. We

encourage you to be aware when you leave the Services and to read

the privacy statements of each and every resource that may collect

Personal Information.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Information security</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

We secure information you provide on computer servers in a

controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access,

use, or disclosure. We maintain reasonable administrative,

technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against

unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of Personal

Information in our control and custody. However, no data

transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be

guaranteed.

</p\>

<p\>

Therefore, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you

acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of

the Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security,

integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged

between you and the Services cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any

such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit

by a third party, despite best efforts.

</p\>

<p\>

As the security of Personal Information depends in part on the

security of the device you use to communicate with us and the

security you use to protect your credentials, please take

appropriate measures to protect this information.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Data breach</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

In the event we become aware that the security of the Services has

been compromised or Users’ Personal Information has been disclosed

to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity,

including, but not limited to, security attacks or fraud, we reserve

the right to take reasonably appropriate measures, including, but

not limited to, investigation and reporting, as well as notification

to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities. In the event of

a data breach, we will make reasonable efforts to notify affected

individuals if we believe that there is a reasonable risk of harm to

the User as a result of the breach or if notice is otherwise

required by law. When we do, we will send you an email.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Changes and amendments</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

We reserve the right to modify this Policy or its terms related to

the Services at any time at our discretion. When we do, we will

revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We may also

provide notice to you in other ways at our discretion, such as

through the contact information you have provided.

</p\>

<p\>

An updated version of this Policy will be effective immediately upon

the posting of the revised Policy unless otherwise specified. Your

continued use of the Services after the effective date of the

revised Policy (or such other act specified at that time) will

constitute your consent to those changes. However, we will not,

without your consent, use your Personal Information in a manner

materially different than what was stated at the time your Personal

Information was collected.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Acceptance of this policy</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

You acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its

terms and conditions. By accessing and using the Services and

submitting your information you agree to be bound by this Policy. If

you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not

authorized to access or use the Services.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<div\>

<h2\>Contacting us</h2\>

<div\>

<p\>

If you have any questions, concerns, or complaints regarding this

Policy, the information we hold about you, or if you wish to

exercise your rights, we encourage you to contact us using the

details below:

</p\>

<p\>info&#64;&#103;d&#101;&#118;&#115;&#46;&#105;o</p\>

<p\>

We will attempt to resolve complaints and disputes and make every

reasonable effort to honor your wish to exercise your rights as

quickly as possible and in any event, within the timescales provided

by applicable data protection laws.

</p\>

</div\>

</div\>

<p\>This document was last updated on August 16, 2021</p\>

</\>

);

};

export default memo(PrivacyPolicy);

Footer
------

[](https://github.com/ "GitHub")© 2024 GitHub, Inc.

### Footer navigation

* Manage cookies
* Do not share my personal information

You can’t perform that action at this time.
